tamiyausa.com 2012-06-30

# TamiyaUSA.com Privacy Statement

| Use **GOOGLE** to search the site  
---  

---  
| 6/22 F104 Version II Detailed Overview |   
| 6/19 Thinning Tamiya Paints |   
| 6/5 Builder Showcase #79 |   
More News... |   
|   
  
---|---  
---  
|  Jul 22  |   
|  TCS Race #175 - Jackson, NJ  |   
|  Jul 29  |   
|  TCS Race #176 - Lynnwood, WA  |   
|  Oct 13-14  |   
|  High Voltage R/C Monster Truck Championships - Cleveland, OH  |   
Past Events... |   

| Privacy Statement  
---  
| Tamiya America, Inc. (TamiyaUSA.com) recognizes privacy and security as being a concern for most individuals and businesses accessing the Internet. Whether you are seeking specific information about one of our quality products, or just browsing our website, we want to make you comfortable with our privacy policy and the security measures we take to protect your information.  
---  
 **How can you correct any inaccuracies in your information?**  
If you would like to correct, change or view any information you have provided, or remove your name from any of our mailings, please contact us.  
 **What information is collected?**  
Tamiya America, Inc. (TamiyaUSA.com) collects identifiable business information, including name, title, company, address, e-mail address, phone numbers, etc. when a consumer registers with us. In addition to inquiries, we may ask you for information at other times, including by way of example, when you enter a sweepstakes, contest or promotion sponsored by Tamiya America Inc. (TamiyaUSA.com) or when you complete surveys or other questionnaires. Wherever Tamiya America, Inc. (TamiyaUSA.com) collects your information we try to include a link to this Privacy Statement on that page.  
 **Who is collecting the information?**  
When you are browsing TamiyaUSA.com and are asked to provide any information, you are sharing that information with Tamiya America, Inc., a wholly owned subsidiary of Tamiya, Inc. Tamiya America, Inc. will only provide information to Tamiya, Inc., if requested. TamiyaUSA.com may contain various links to third party web sites. Third party web sites may provide additional information, goods, services and/or promotions. Third party web sites are owned and operated independently of Tamiya America, Inc. (TamiyaUSA.com) and have their own separate privacy statement and data collection practices. Any information you provide to third party web sites will be governed under the terms of their privacy policy, if any. Tamiya America, Inc. has no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the independent actions or policies of third party web sites and is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such sites.  
 **How is my information used?**  
TamiyaUSA.com may contain optional surveys and questionnaires asking for information, as well as several opportunities for visitors to ask questions. We use the information you provide to help us design and build better products and to provide advice and purchase recommendations. Taking part in any of these segments is always optional. We also use the information we collect to help target valuable marketing and advertising offers. This kind of advertising may be done with banner ads as well as promotional e-mails sent by Tamiya America, Inc. Finally, Tamiya America, Inc. does research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us during a promotion, from surveys and from our server log files. We do this to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis so as to prevent identification of information relating to any one individual. Tamiya America, Inc. will only share this aggregate data with Tamiya, Inc., if requested.  
 **With whom does Tamiya America, Inc. share my information?**  
Except as outlined in this policy or on our web site, Tamiya America, Inc. (TamiyaUSA.com) will never provide your information to third parties without your consent. Tamiya America, Inc. may share information with Tamiya, Inc. as requested. Tamiya America, Inc. may also disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the TamiyaUSA.com Terms of Use or may be violating Tamiya America, Inc. or others' rights or causing injury to or interference with Tamiya America, Inc. or others' property. Tamiya America, Inc. may also disclose or access information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. Tamiya America, Inc. may match user information with third party data to help us better understand our customers. However, Tamiya America, Inc. will only use this information internally and will not disclose any of your information to third party interests.  
 **What choices do I have regarding collection, use and distribution of my information?**  
Tamiya America, Inc. may, from time to time, send you e-mail or direct mail regarding our products and services. If you do not wish to receive such information, simply tell us when you give us your information, or follow the directions contained on it to remove your name from our mailing. On certain types of Tamiya America, Inc. (TamiyaUSA.com) promotions, we will ask for your e-mail address in order to contact you in the event you have won a prize. When you participate in these types of promotions, you may automatically receive promotion related e-mail. Occasionally these promotion related e-mail messages might include targeted advertisements. If you do not wish to receive such advertisements, you can choose not to participate in such promotions or contests.  
 **What security measures does Tamiya America, Inc. use to protect my information from loss, misuse or alteration?**  
When you provide information to Tamiya America, Inc. your information is located on a secured server. In reality, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, Tamiya America, Inc. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our Web Site, and therefore, you use our web site at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we use our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.  
 **Unsubscribing.**  
You can unsubscribe or change your subscription to any of our notification services at any time.  
 **Additional Information**  
Questions regarding this policy should be directed to customer service.  
Rev. 11/05  
Back To Top
